LUKE ANDREW THOMAS

ADDRESS:	Santa Clara, CA	<u>Емаіі</u> :	LATHOMAS 5 @ USFCA. EDU	Website:	APAPERADAY.COM
<i>Linkedin</i> : w	WW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/LUKETHOMAS	GITHUB:	GITHUB.COM/TUKAVIC	MOBILE:	PLEASE USE EMAIL

Machine Learning Engineer with a Master's Degree in Data Science. Experience using deep learning to deliver solutions and exploring current techniques in deep learning while maintaining a blog summarizing deep learning papers with over 90+ posts to date.

EDUCATION

M.S.D.S. UNIVERSITY OF SAN FRANCISCO

August 2021

- Ongoing Master's of Data Science
- <u>Select Courses</u>: Data Acquisition, Relational Databases, Distributed Data Systems, EDA and Visualization, Linear Regression, Advanced Machine Learning, Time Series Analysis, Data Structures & Algorithms
- <u>ML algorithm implementations from scratch in Python</u>: Regularized Linear and Logistic Regression with Gradient Descent, Naive Bayes, Decision Trees, Random Forest, K-means Clustering, Boosting, Deep Neural Networks, RNN, recommendation engine, and automated feature selection algorithms.

B.S.E.E GROVE CITY COLLEGE

May 2014

- Graduated with Bachelors of Electrical Engineering with emphasis on Computer Engineering
- Select Courses: Computer Architecture, Operating Systems, C++ I and II, Data Comm and Networking

WORK EXPERIENCE

W.L. GORE AND ASSOCIATES— Santa Clara, CA NLP Data Scientist Intern

January 2021 - Present

Transformed a wishful idea into a working GUI which scales to analyze over 100+ pdf pages into a graphical interface using Zero-Shot Learning, reducing delivery times from hours to minutes.

- Manually generated custom dataset annotated with Negative Sampling techniques
- Utilized BERT Transformer architecture embeddings to make Zero-Shot Learning predictions.
- Additionally, implemented a querying interface with the Transformer model to search a corpus highlighting pertinent text from naturally formed queries, enabling semantic search over business documents.

DIALOG SEMICONDUCTOR- Santa Clara, CA

2016 - 2020

Field Applications Engineer

Support hardware design engineers in all phases of the design cycle including introductions, design creation, timely support, and failure analysis. Close coordination is required with all customers due to product programmability.

• Introduced leading networking company to product technology as well as provided full technical support to increase design wins from 0 to 10+ with as well as collaborated reference designs

SILEGO TECHNOLOGY (ACQUIRED BY DIALOG IN 2017) – Santa Clara, CA

2014 - 2016

Applications Engineer

Create customized design configurations for FPGA-like product per customer design requirements. Job duties include custom configuration work, custom datasheet documentation, failure analysis, communicating with FAEs, and investigation of new applications.